{
    "question": "buatin sinopsis film cloudy a chance of meatballs 2 dong pake bhs indonesia gpp..nanti aku yang translate sendiri...tolong bantu ya",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "It&#039;s always been Flint&#039;s dream \nto be recognized as a great inventor, but everything changes when he \ndiscovers that his most infamous machine (which turns water into food) \nis still operating and is now creating food-animal hybrids - \n\"foodimals!\" With the fate of humanity in his hands, Chester sends Flint\n and his friends on a dangerously delicious mission - to battle hungry \ntacodiles, shrimpanzees, hippotatomuses, cheespiders and other food \ncreatures to save the world again!            \n                <span>- <span>Written by\nColumbia Pictures</span></span>        \n            <span>\nFlint Lockwood is a genius who created a machine that turns water into \nfood which went out of control. Flint would stop it. He would set out to\n build his own lab with Sam Sparks. But Chester V, the scientist who \ninspired Flint comes to the island to clean up the mess, the machine \nmade, and offers Flint a job at his lab. Flint takes it. Later, Dr. V \ntells him that the machine is now creating living food\n and they could be a threat. So he goes back to the island along with \nhis friends including Sam to stop it. But Sam tells flint that they \ncould acting hastily but Dr. V convinces Flint otherwise. So they leave \nFlint and eventually learn the truth.            </span><br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "descriptive-tentang-aula-987",
            "question": "Descriptive tentang aula",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>ruang besar atau pendapa (di gedung sekolah dsb) untuk berapat, mengadakan upacara, dsb<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "hall is a room that used for many kinds of activity. like for meeting or workshop<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-translate-ke-dalam-bahasa-indonesia-kata-kata-dibawah-ini-822",
            "question": "tolong translate ke dalam bahasa indonesia, kata-kata dibawah ini... Salam perkenalan, selamat bergabung dengan perusahaan kami. Mari kita berjuang sama-sama untuk kemajuan perusahaan dan kesejahteraan para karyawan dan karyawati diperusahaan kita. Dan mari kita sama-sama mempersiapkan tanggungjawab atas kemajuan perusahaan ini.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Salam perkenalan, selamat bergabung dengan perusahaan kami. Mari kita berjuang sama-sama untuk kemajuan perusahaan dan kesejahteraan para karyawan dan karyawati diperusahaan kita. Dan mari kita sama-sama mempersiapkan tanggungjawab atas kemajuan perusahaan ini.<br><br></span>Introductory greetings, congratulations join our company. Let&#039;s fight together for the progress and welfare of the employees of the company and an employee of the company we are. And let us equally the responsibility for preparing the company&#039;s progress.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Introductory greetings, congratulations join our company. Let&#039;s struggle are equally for the progress and welfare of the employees of the company and an employee of the company we are. And let us equally the responsibility for preparing this company&#039;s progress<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-the-jumbled-words-to-form-meaningful-sentencesstarting-w-193",
            "question": "arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words. 1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place 2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a \u00a0 mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "2. Mr. Kukuh and his family will go to Bali and Lombok if they have a long holiday this year<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-pengertian-dari-direction-text-tolong-ya-aku-search-gak-n-672",
            "question": "Apa pengertian dari direction text ? tolong ya , aku search gak nemu-nemu niih",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "text yg menunjukkkan arah kali<br>direction kan arah/tujuan<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-beri-penjelasan-tentang-word-order-dengan-rinci-844",
            "question": "Tolong Beri Penjelasan Tentang Word Order\u00a0Dengan Rinci",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Word order atau tata urut kata merupakan cara untuk\nmenyusun kata \u2013 kata dalam urutan atau susunan yang tepat dan benar. </span>\n\n<br><br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Word order adalah susunan kata-kata dalam kalimat, artinya bahwa cara kita menempatkan setiap kata itu haruslah sesuai dengan fungsinya dalam membentuk suatu kalimat. Caranya dengan mengetahui dan menghafal rumus atau pola baku.<br>Contoh:<br>&#039;&#039; Sebuah mobil mewah baru buatan Amerika Serikat &#039;&#039; diterjemahkan menjadi \" A new American car \".<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-contoh-berita-acara-serah-terima-pekerjaan-proyek-558",
            "question": "Ada yang tau contoh Berita Acara Serah Terima Pekerjaan (Proyek) dalam bahasa Inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><em>Handover Works (Project</em><span><em>)</em></span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-326",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Me : Mom, you are so beautiful in this night.\nMom : really? You never told me before mommy use beauty fash.\nMe : yes mom, you are A princess for daddy tonight, let tell Daddy, if Daddy shock, ask A opinion about you mom.\nMom : Ok , thankyou my sweetheart, i love you.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "choose-inappropriate-structure-in-the-following-sentences-or-dial-968",
            "question": "choose inappropriate structure in the following sentences or dialog below ! man : how's your new job at the hospital ? \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 A woman : it's great and my co-workers sre so nice \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 C man : good. that's important for you to feel exciting with your workers \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0D",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>man : good. that&#039;s important for you to feel <u>exciting</u> with your workers</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-kata-sifat-dari-pengelompokan-tersebut-sebanyak-banyak-851",
            "question": "Sebutkan kata sifat dari pengelompokan tersebut! (sebanyak-banyaknya)    menurut:1.Skin (Cool, Ho, ...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 2. Place (in,at,on,\u00a0...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 3. Age (New,old,\u00a0...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 4. Nose (sweet, smelling, ...)\r\n\r\nTolong kerjasamanya Friend's.. thanks so'much!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Skin = cool, hot, soft, dirty, clean, rude, ugly, beautiful\nPlace : in, on, at, beside, behind, in front, between.\nAge : old, young, new,",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}